<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Turning the Other Cheek</title>
    <description>Wayne&#39;s story about fighting colorectal cancer.</description>
    <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://waynehahn.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:32:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:32:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Near The End Of The Road Part One</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/decfamselfie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;December Family Selfie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our final chemo treatment was over back on December 30, 2015.  None of us miss it, especially Wayne. We do miss visiting with Dr. Donehower, Wayne’s oncologist, with his meticulous care and positive personality!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our next appointment was with our Colorectal Surgeon, Dr. Efron, gave Wayne the news that he would not need radiation and that surgery could be planned.  Dr. He, his liver specialist, came in to tell us that since they cannot find the cancer on he liver!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The surgery will go something like this:  Dr. He will give Wayne a sonogram in surgery to be certain that it is gone and not hiding anywhere. If it is hiding, he will cut it out and if it is not there, Wayne &amp;amp; his liver will be checked on a regular basis.  When Dr. He has finished, Dr. Efron will take over and take out he cancerous part of the colon. The surgery will take approximately 4-5 hours. The date of surgery Wayne’s surgery will be March 18th, he will be in the hospital 5-7 days &amp;amp; hoping recovery will be tolerable!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have been blessed with a wonderful Colorectal Team at Johns Hopkins, all of the specialists, their assistants, the chemo team at Green Spring, and Tam from Dr. Efron’s Team. They were so open to our questions and they accepted us as Wayne’s team too!
Your caring and prayers has gotten Wayne this far and we hope you will continue to keep Wayne in your prayers through he next phase. Funny thing is – Wayne has never been in the hospital - he still has his tonsils!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/near-the-end-of-the-road-part-one</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/near-the-end-of-the-road-part-one</guid>
        
        
        <category>treatment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy New Year to All</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/wnfcelebrate.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wayne and Frani enjoying vino at Grand Cru&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year to everyone!  As always we thank you for all your prayers, all of your well-wishes, all of your support.  We have some really good news for you.  As good as Wayne’s CEA count was last time, it gets even better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne went for a CT scan along with his bloodwork on Monday.  Today he is having his 4th round of chemo.  Before he has chemo, Dr. Donehower, his oncologist, meets with us to discuss the results of his labwork.  Today’s discussion included his CT scan.  We are proud to say that there is no trace of cancer on his liver.  He said Wayne’s liver specialist, Dr. He, will still remove that sliver of his liver where the cancer was (in this case it’s good to use past tense!).   The cancer on the lower colon area has &lt;em&gt;SHRUNK&lt;/em&gt;!!!!  It has gone from 1.5cm to 1.0cm in thickness!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Donehower said that he couldn’t believe 2 months into treatment,  Wayne would have as good an outcome as that so soon.  He also said that the conversation begins of curing Wayne of cancer.  Dr. Donehower has a tiny office, and it got smaller by four wide smiles in that room!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctors will have a conference next week about Wayne to decide if he will have radiation next.  Life is progressing on a very positive note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne must be feeling good, he’s been joking around with the nurses.  He did all he could this morning before the chemo.  He took out the trash, cleaned out the litter boxes, made us breakfast.  Nikki even had him make mashed potatoes for tonight.  We will post of picture later of how he will look when we leave chemo today.  He will resemble the Invisible Man, by the time he leaves.  Why?  There is a story that we didn’t share with you last time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(From last treatment):  We were riding high from the good news about Wayne’s CEA count.  In the midst of chemo we were toying with the idea of having lunch after.  We blocked out how bad the Oxalyplaten makes him feel.  It’s immediate when the symptoms kick in.  He’s pretty miserable for the following days.  Being one not to complain, he stayed mum on some strange things he experienced while the Oxalyplaten was being infused during the 2 hours.  We finished &amp;amp; left.  On the way down we talked of stopping at Eddie’s to get a few items.  As soon as the door opened to a breezy 45 degree day, Wayne didn’t look right.  3/4 of the way to the car, he started sneezing.  With that his throat closed up, he turned red then purple and kept gasping for air.  It was awful.  Nikki &amp;amp; I got him back up to the chemo area.  You never saw so many nurses go right into action.  One rolled over a chair halfway across the room, another grabbed an iv, and put it in him, and the rest were either monitoring/helping him or getting the doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you remember when we said that the doctor warned us about the cold?  I think the 3 of us took it that he would get cold, not that the cold would &lt;em&gt;get&lt;/em&gt; him.  One of the side effects from Oxalyplaten is that when cold air hits the face/neck, your throat closes.  We will never forget that again.  Today he will wear a full ski mask, scarf &amp;amp; be entirely zipped up.  No chances taken this time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As soon as we hear word from Dr. Efron, his colorectal surgeon, we will post again.  Meanwhile the 3 of us wish you a happy holiday season.  Be safe, be merry, be healthy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From our family to you,
Happy 2016,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With love, Frani, Wayne &amp;amp; Nikki&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/happy-new-year</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/happy-new-year</guid>
        
        
        <category>treatment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holiday Comes Early For Us</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/images/drvisit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dr. Donehower and Wayne&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came into this chemo with a little trepidation. Dr. Donehower would let us know about Wayne’s CEA count.  The normal range is 3.0 or below. Prior to treatment, Wayne’s number was 17. We were upset at how high the number was.  Dr. Donehower said even though it was high, the numbers could have been a lot worse. As long as Wayne’s system responded to treatment, his chances of conquering the cancer demons looked optimistic. I am proud to share with you that he dropped from &lt;strong&gt;17 to 7&lt;/strong&gt; with 2 chemo treatments!!!  Even the chemo nurses were happy when they saw his numbers.
We thank you for keeping Wayne in your prayers. Someone above is definitely listening.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/holiday-comes-early-for-us</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/holiday-comes-early-for-us</guid>
        
        
        <category>treatment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Shave November</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/whisker-wayne.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Whisker-Wayne&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, Nikki decided that for the Prostate Cancer Awareness Month, Wayne should join the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.no-shave.org/&quot;&gt;No Shave November&lt;/a&gt;.  That didn’t take too much persuasion!  He looks cute, older but still real cute.  His skin is very sensitive and he was advised to refrain from shaving.  He might not be shaving, but that extra bit still needs some styling.  He’s not ready for “Whisker Wars” yet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne’s white blood count dropped a bit this month.  It should be 4.50 but it is 4.03.  This may be the reason for his short naps!  😊&lt;br /&gt;
He looks wonderful, always ready to go somewhere &amp;amp; he refuses to stay home to lay around.  He remains so positive which makes life much easier for Nikki and I.  When he is doing good, we are doing good.  I do believe that God put us on this earth to be caretakers and we are good at that job, after 4 parents, Nikki’s bout with breast cancer and now Wayne, I believe all that should have earned us the halo, at least!  👼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne’s completed part of his second cycle of his chemo treatment.  The first day is the chemo infusion, Oxaliplatin, along with the oral pills, Xeloda, that he continues to take 6 pills a day for 2 weeks.  It’s like reliving Nikki’s bout again in that there are plenty of Gatorades, mashed potatoes homemade soups &amp;amp; homemade noodles, crackers etc.  True to her word, Nikki has started her mashed potatoes repayment to Wayne.  He made them so many times for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He will be tired Wednesday’s chemo through Sunday, then we can start going out to eat again and taking our walks.  By the 3rd week, he is on a mission to get things done. His latest cravings are turkey and gravy with fries or mashed potatoes.  Last week we tried 3 different places (the Diner, Greenspring Inn &amp;amp; Joey Dee’s Lounge) &amp;amp; decided his favorite was at Joey Dee’s Lounge, off Loch Raven Blvd.  It’s one of our favorite places for comfort food.  We are looking forward to his next craving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also had an appointment with Dr. Donehower, his most compassionate oncologist, which went well.  He is a really a caring physician.  He said he really hoped the treatments Wayne is undergoing are working as well since  his attitude and physical fortitude are going strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bumps Along the Road&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess it couldn’t all go so perfect.  On Friday Wayne woke up in the early morning with cramps in his calves.  The pain was intense.  We tried the heating pad but by 6 pm he couldn’t take it anymore.  Nikki &amp;amp; I took him to GBMC Emergency upon advice from doctor on duty at Hopkins.  We needed to get his electrolytes checked and to make sure there weren’t any blood clots (which unfortunately is a very real side affect from the chemo). Luckily it was a visit that clocked under 4 hours!  Nikki &amp;amp; I were a wreck that he’d pick up germs, but would not wear a face mask!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nikki’s retelling:&lt;/em&gt;
&amp;gt;”He’s our rock, so it’s really been hard for me to adjust to seeing him sometimes get weakened by the Oxaliplatin.  But you would love, even though he can’t touch anything cold, he quickly puts on his gloves to open doors for mom &amp;amp; I.  Even when we went to the hospital &amp;amp; he could barely walk, he refused being dropped off or being transported in a wheel chair.  Even going in, he held the door for Mom &amp;amp; me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all the doctor on charge said to just rest and use the heating pad for the pain in his calves.  This was just another side effect from the chemo infusion drug. Whew. 🙀 Never a dull moment around here!  But it could be worse so we are not complaining.  Just, please remember to get your colonoscopy.  Don’t wait for 10 years.  Remember that Wayne had no symptoms, it doesn’t run in his family.  It just showed up like an unwelcome guest who sneaked in and doesn’t want to leave.  There is a CAE blood test to check that out.  I’m not sure why it’s not a routine check for all of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have found from the last 2 cycles that his first week isn’t great after the Oxaliplatin infusion but we are hopeful that it will be strong enough to kill the red cells more that the white cells.  We can take 1 week of bad.  It’s better than 10 days or 2 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope you all had a great week!  Remember how much You mean to Us and Thank You for listening.  Happy Thanksgiving to you and yours!  Sending Love to all of you. 💙💙💙&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/no-shave-november</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/no-shave-november</guid>
        
        
        <category>treatment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And The Beat Goes On</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/wayne_vino.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wayne @ VNo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne just keeps rolling on….  The first 4 days after his chemo “in-house” (fluid and nausea infusion), Wayne had every symptom that his doctor &amp;amp; nurse mentioned.  We thought he was pulling our leg at first. Who reading this doesn’t know Wayne as a jokester, right??  He put his hands on the steering wheel and then later in the evening when he went into the refrigerator, the cold felt like it was a burning sensation on his hands.  Odd, isn’t it. But that is a major side effect from his Xelox combination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day, guess what we did?  We went out and purchased some jersey gloves so he could stay independent &amp;amp; used the fridge (and other cold spots) at his convenience.  He was queasy and was getting fatigued easily.  He wasn’t happy about it, but we were taking care of him - fixing his drinks, cooking, taking out the trash. He was not content because he likes to take care of us. After several days he was feeling much like his old self. He started cooking &amp;amp; doing his routine things. The minute he was telling Nikki &amp;amp; I how to do things, we knew he was feeling much better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We try to walk every day.  We ate out last night for the first time since the night before chemo and he was without his queasiness!  He only has 4 more days of pills then he gets a week long reprieve.  We may travel to the beach for a few days depending on the weather.  He is enjoying the phones calls, texts &amp;amp; emails from our friends.  We can’t thank you enough for your continued love and support!  I don’t know how people go through this kind of stress without their faith and the people that they love.  Keep the faith, keep him in your prayers and keep in touch!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/and-the-beat-goes-on</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/and-the-beat-goes-on</guid>
        
        
        <category>treatment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eat Dirt Cancer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/wayne-nikki-first-chemo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dad and I at JHU chemo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would have thought we were getting ready for a trip.  Everyone got up &amp;amp; got ready without the usual dreary morning feeling.  Even in the waking hours we remain positive.  Only the cats were confused when we left, “where are our treats?”  “Where is our mound of food.”  They know the only time the 3 of us leave that early, it must mean trip which equals tons of food for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were the first ones at the chemo center.  Even though we weren’t much for being there so early, it turned out to be a good thing.  We had more private time with our nurse.  To be honest, once you’ve done chemo at Mercy, there’s no comparison.  Mercy is so darn upbeat as are the chemo nurses.  Even dealing with the type of job they have, the nurses still make you feel good.  I still love to pop in the chemo area and say hi to the nurses when I am down there.  It’s a little more business like at the Hopkins Greenspring center.  But we had a lovely nurse, Linda, who took care of Dad.  Best for Dad was that she inserted the Pic line on first try &amp;amp; he hardly felt it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It takes about 4 hours, which is much better than my all day treatment.  I was leery Dad would be super sick since he doesn’t get much for pre-meds.  It must relate to they type of treatment he’s getting.  He’s done just fine as far as sickness and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The odd symptom which is most prevalent in his treatment is that he reacts to cold.  “???”  I bet that’s what you’re thinking.  We were too.  If he goes into the refrigerator, he cannot just pick up something.  Why?  It like an extreme prickly feeling he told us.  He needs to use gloves to maneuver around the refrigerator these days.  And his feet need to be covered when  he’s walking, because the cold floor affects him as well.  Likewise for when he drinks or anything cold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brrr.  His reaction to cold seems to be the worst he dealt with on Day One of treatment.  I’ve been keeping a calendar for him that he can record his general feeling each day.  They say how you feel from the beginning to the end of each treatment cycle is pretty much the same each time.  I did that during my treatment &amp;amp; it really helped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Water.  I told Dad if he can drink 3 Camelbak water bottles a day, he’ll be so far ahead of the game.  And he needed to drink hot lemon water to flush out evil toxins.  We’ll try to eat as clean as possible so that the chemo can kill the bad stuff &amp;amp; we won’t let anymore sugars and stuff like that slow it down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walking.  I preach to everyone to walk walk walk.  Even if you can walk up &amp;amp; down the street, that’s good.  One of the first people with cancer I knew was going through a heavy chemo.  After each round, she would come home and walk her dog around Patterson Park. She walked daily.  I did the same even when it was snowing, and I credit that not only to coping, but to conquering the demons that try to come up when you go through chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has 12 days left of his oral chemo pills, and then a week off.  Thankfully it’s been an uneventful experience.  What has made this momentous has been the continuing love &amp;amp; positive words of encouragement you have sent to him.  We even have a friend who is doing distant Reiki on him.  As we always seem to end these posts, we thank all of you.  Your love and support helps give us the strength to handle this “blip” in our life.  We pray it’s a small enough journey that it is nothing more than a footnote in our life’s history.  When we look back, what we want most to remember is how wonderful you all were to us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/eat-dirt-cancer</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/eat-dirt-cancer</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meds Have Arrived</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/mom-dad-fenwick.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wayne and Frani enjoying time in Fenwick Island, DE&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We waited patiently for Wayne’s chemo pills to arrive all day from the Pharmacy.  Someone had to be home to sign for them so we took turns running errands for the weekend.  We finally had an 7:45pm delivery.
While waiting we made a wonderful Shrimp Etoufée over rice for dinner.  I also made 3 apple/walnut cakes, 2 for gifts and one for us!  Even though the pills have arrived, Wayne cannot take them until Wednesday morning, his first chemo appointment.  He sees his oncologist to get his first infusion.  He is on a regime where he continues to take the pills daily for 14 days, then have 7 free days. He will continue this regime 3-4 times.  Hopefully this will shrink his tumor and kill the c cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne has been upbeat most of the time - except when anxiety decides to pay him a visit, which I believe is normal.  We are blessed with our special friends, who keep us busy with social functions &amp;amp; help us to lead a normal life.  We are looking forward to a long weekend in Florida &amp;amp; a few other quick getaways as long as Wayne tolerates the meds.  We only think positive in our home!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The few drawbacks are that there are some friends who tell me that they don’t know what to say.  You can only say “ I don’t know what to say except that I am here if you need me”. There are never the perfect words when you know someone who is special in your life and you know they are in peril.  Just think positive with a smile. Wayne is on the phone more than Nikki &amp;amp; I together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wayne has really been overwhelmed at the outpouring of notes, emails, phone calls &amp;amp; getting together.  We have a big crew of warriors helping us fight this fight. Please know how much we appreciate you!  It would be so hard to go through this without you.  Love is in the air……..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/meds-have-arrived</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/meds-have-arrived</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Plan</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/lovebirds.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Lovebirds&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our oncologist is starting Wayne on a chemo pill combination called Xelox. 14 days on, 7 days off for the next 12 weeks.  The side effects are usually minimal, mild nauseau and hand/foot syndrome.  What is that?  It’s sensitivity to cold in his fingertips and his toes.  Nikki &amp;amp; I are in disbelief about the latter symptom because I refer to him as my heating pad.  For once I may get my dream of an electric blanket!  Nikki had a similar reaction and everything had to be luke warm.  The good thing for Wayne is
that he gets to be home throughout the regimen.  He’ll still need to go in from time to time for blood tests to make sure his counts are doing well.  He should not lose hair either.  Nikki started buying him hats just in case!
After the 12 weeks, more blood tests and some scans to see if it is has been effective.  He is happy about that.  Wayne’s attitude is very upbeat and positive.  He’s ready to squash those cancer cells!&lt;br /&gt;
His oncologist, Dr Donehower, is personable and caring.  He told Wayne he could tell that he had a good support system with us. That made us feel good!  So please continue to pray for him, that the treatment will be effective enough to get him through to the next step.  We cannot thank our friends and family enough for all of your support!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/the-plan</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/the-plan</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Waiting Game</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The hardest part of every illness is the waiting game. Waiting for appointments, waiting for results &amp;amp; waiting, waiting,waiting.  We wouldn’t dare complain as we were so fortunate to get in with our doctors. Johns Hopkins is so different than I thought it would be.  We absolutely loved Mercy when Nikki started her treatments 4 years ago.  There wasn’t one thing about Mercy that we didn’t like.  Surprisingly, Hopkins has gained that “patient care” attitude.  We felt like we were the only patients there.  They could not be more caring.  As of now, the liver specialist, Dr. He, felt the spot was very small and he would take it out after chemo and radiation.  Our mode for Wayne is going to be 6 weeks of chemo, 6 weeks of radiation and 12 weeks off.  After that, Wayne will have surgery.  We feel very confident in our doctors and Wayne has a wonderful positive outlook.  We will get him through this.  We thank all our family and friends for their support. Wayne has been humbled by all the out pouring of prayers, notes &amp;amp; cards.  We are blessed!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 02:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/the-waiting-game</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/the-waiting-game</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Wayne&#39;s Journey!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve provided a way for you to stay updated on Wayne’s progress.  We’ll try to keep this as current as possible.  We thank you for your prayers and support throughout this part of our life.  We couldn’t do it without you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 05:45:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/welcome</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/welcome</guid>
        
        
        <category>welcome</category>
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
