<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Turning the Other Cheek</title>
    <description>Wayne&#39;s story about fighting colorectal cancer.</description>
    <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://waynehahn.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 14:28:38 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 14:28:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Waiting Game</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The hardest part of every illness is the waiting game. Waiting for appointments, waiting for results &amp;amp; waiting, waiting,waiting.  We wouldn’t dare complain as we were so fortunate to get in with our doctors. Johns Hopkins is so different than I thought it would be.  We absolutely loved Mercy when Nikki started her treatments 4 years ago.  There wasn’t one thing about Mercy that we didn’t like.  Surprisingly, Hopkins has gained that “patient care” attitude.  We felt like we were the only patients there.  They could not be more caring.  As of now, the liver specialist, Dr. He, felt the spot was very small and he would take it out after chemo and radiation.  Our mode for Wayne is going to be 6 weeks of chemo, 6 weeks of radiation and 12 weeks off.  After that, Wayne will have surgery.  We feel very confident in our doctors and Wayne has a wonderful positive outlook.  We will get him through this.  We thank all our family and friends for their support. Wayne has been humbled by all the out pouring of prayers, notes &amp;amp; cards.  We are blessed!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 02:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/the-waiting-game</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/the-waiting-game</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Wayne&#39;s Journey!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve provided a way for you to stay updated on Wayne’s progress.  We’ll try to keep this as current as possible.  We thank you for your prayers and support throughout this part of our life.  We couldn’t do it without you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 05:45:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/welcome</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/welcome</guid>
        
        
        <category>welcome</category>
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Optimistic and Strong</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we feel very optimistic &amp;amp; strong. We are keeping positive. Wayne’s appointment with the Liver specialist is on Friday so we will update after that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/optimistic-and-strong</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/optimistic-and-strong</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MRI Results</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Results are in. They found a small lesion on Wayne’s liver. We were quite devastated but they feel that they can do surgery to remove it. The Doctors feel like between chemo, radiation and surgery, this cancer can be removed over a 6-8 month period&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/mri-results</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/mri-results</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waiting Stage</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I guess you can imagine the power of anxiety waiting for results.  We have decided to get up everyday and keep busy, meet with friends, go out to lunch and/or dinner, just keep moving and worry less.  Wayne had his CAT scan, PET scan &amp;amp; finally his MRI this past Sunday.  Johns Hopkins has a wonderful campus.  It’s like an airport without luggage!  Nikki &amp;amp; I found one of the really nice courtyards while Wayne was getting his tests.  We packed our iPhones, iPads, crosswords, bottles of water and made ourselves comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exploring the buildings, Nikki and I found the Dome area and the statue of Christ in the original main entrance (located on Broadway).  The artwork throughout Johns Hopkins is amazing.  We had plenty of time to explore during all of his tests.  We have spent most of our time in the Zayed Building waiting….. Hopkins is an incredible place.  We feel blessed, strong and are really optimistic that Wayne will get the care that he needs to beat this disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://waynehahn.github.io/img/jhjesus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Divine Healer by Danish sculptor, Bertel Thorvaldsen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- begin blurb --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the Jesus statue known as the “Divine Healer” or “Christ the Consoler.” The Carrera marble Jesus has arms outstretched, open in a gesture of welcome to all who wander in.
&lt;!--end blurb  --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/waiting-stage</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/waiting-stage</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s Next</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We were recommended to see Dr. Donehower and Dr. Efron at Johns Hopkins by a friend. What a blessing that turned out to be. Wayne felt immediately comforted by their plan of action. A week of tests followed. Currently we are in the waiting stage for results. We were told that there were spots on his lung and liver but that could be scar tissue, we hope!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 05:45:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/whats-next</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/whats-next</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Beginning</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On 9/2/2015, we created this site to keep it a little more personal than Facebook. Wayne had a routine visit for a colonoscopy. We found out immediately that our gastroenterologist, Dr. Corkum, said it appeared it was cancer in his colon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://waynehahn.github.io/the-beginning</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://waynehahn.github.io/the-beginning</guid>
        
        
        <category>pre</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
